Your Watching this on Gospel App
War.
It's been a part of humanity in every age.
We fight for power,
for riches,
for rights or for freedom.
There always seems to be
something to fight for.
But one thing has remained
true of every war.
Behind the field of battle,
someone has developed a strategy.
This was part of my husband's role
in the army.
He would look at what the enemy was doing,
then begin putting together the resources
and a plan to fight against them.
He was a crucial part of this process
until a heart attack claimed his life.
That was a hard time for me and our son.
I was reminded that death
is a part of life,
and that the life we're given
should never be taken for granted.
It's been 40 years since Leo passed,
but I still hold on to the many lessons
I learned from that time.
I find myself amazed that
of the many battles we engage in today,
be it money, control or
matters of the heart,
very few of us
know how to fight the right way,
or understand
who we're really fighting against.
To win any battle,
you've got to have
the right strategy and resources,
because victories don't come by accident.
Hey, Mom, I gotta go. Yeah.
All right, okay. Bye.
Jason and David, get rid of the ball
and help me with these boxes!
Om.
Oh! I am so sorry.
You must be Elizabeth Jordan.
- I am. And you're Melissa?
- Yes.
I'm sorry. We just started packing.
Oh, no problem. Can I help you with that?
Honey. Honey, I gotta be
in Knoxville at 2:00.
Uh, but I finished the closet.
That was in the refrigerator.
- Real estate agent.
- Software rep.
How did you know that?
It's on that folder
you're holding in your hand.
I would love to stay.
I'm very sorry I have to leave.
My wife can answer everything
about the house.
We realize it's a disaster
and we've agreed to blame it on the kids.
- So, I'll call you later.
- Love you!
I understand. My husband does
the same thing. Pharmaceuticals.
Oh. Does he ever get tired of the travel?
No, I do not.
I enjoy the drive.
Well, we're excited
to do business with you, Tony.
- Hey, tell Coleman I said hello.
- I'll do it.
And, uh, thanks for the new driver.
Hey, you enjoy it, okay?
- I will.
- All right.
Good to see you.
Gentlemen, we'll be in touch.
I see you made the sale.
- Of course.
- I'm impressed.
Most guys run out
with their tail between their legs.
I'm Tony Jordan.
Veronica Drake. I work for Mr. Barnes.
I'll be your contact for the purchase.
Okay. Well, Veronica Drake,
I guess I'll be seeing you again
when I return in two weeks.
I look forward to it.
Mom?
I'm in here, Danielle.
Here's my last report card.
I still got one C.
Oh, baby. You have an A in everything else.
One C in math is not that bad.
At least you get a break
for the summer, right?
Is that your feet?
I'm sorry, baby, I ran out of foot powder.
That smells terrible!
I know, Danielle. I just needed
to take my shoes off for a minute.
That's, like, awful.
Well, don't just sit there looking at them.
Why don't you give me a hand
and rub them right there?
Ew. No way.
Girl, go set
the table for dinner.
When your daddy gets home,
you can show him your report card. Okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
- All right.
I just heard him pull in, Danielle.
Will he be mad about my C?
I already told you, baby,
a C is not that bad. It's okay.
Hey, Daddy.
Hey, Danielle.
I got my last report card.
I made all A's except for one C.
So, I just got a notification
that you moved $5,000
from our savings
into your checking account.
That better not be
so you can prop up your sister again.
You just gave that much money
to your family last month.
And my sister needs it
more than your parents do.
My parents are elderly. Okay?
Your sister married a bum,
and I'm not supporting someone
who's too lazy to work.
Darren is not a bum.
He's just having a
hard time finding a job.
Liz, he is a bum.
Look, I can't even remember
the last time he had a job.
Can we talk about this later?
No, we'll talk about it now.
Because if you want to give them
what you make, that's fine.
- But you're not giving them my money.
- Your money?
The last time I checked,
we both put money into that account.
And the last time I checked,
I make four times what you do.
So you don't move a cent out of that
account without asking me first.
Can we please just eat dinner?
You know what? Go ahead.
I'm going to the gym.
Oh!
Ballgame!
- Whoo-hoo!
- That was sick, man! That was sick.
- You all right, dog?
- Yeah. Why?
You look like you're playing
a little mad tonight.
So? You know that means I play better.
Better means ball hog?
Dude, I can't get a pass from you.
It'd be easier to baptize a cat.
I just needed to blow off
a little steam. Okay?
- Well, I hope you're done.
- I gotta go.
Yo, yo, yo, you're
coming to church, right?
Maybe.
Maybe means no.
Hey, Tony, man. You gotta hit me one.
Come on, man. I gotta go.
Dude, I just told all these guys.
Just one.
Watch this.
Told you!
The favor of God can't be bought,
traded or manipulated.
Because people still come to church
with their hearts
totally distant from the Lord.
But they think they could put on
their Sunday best,
and throw a super spiritual smile
on their face and impress God.
God is looking for people
who will seek him with a whole heart.
So it all comes down to this.
We either seek Him or we don't.
And God surely knows the difference
between the two, and so should we.
Danielle, I have to meet a client
in the morning,
so I'm going to drop you off early
at the community center, okay?
Okay. Can we pick up Jennifer on the way?
Sure, if it's okay with her mother.
Who's Jennifer?
She's on my Double Dutch team.
I thought you were playing basketball.
I wanted to jump rope again.
Tony, you should go see her practice
tomorrow. She's really very good.
I'm out of town this week.
When were you gonna tell me?
I just did.
Tony, I know you're
the company's top salesman,
but in order for this family to function,
we have to communicate.
I thought you'd be here this week.
Well, if you want to continue to live
in this house, I have to make sales.
And that means being flexible.
Aren't you a little too old
to be jumping rope?
Here you go.
Now there's 5, 10, 15, 20.
And here's 5 extra 'cause
I like your haircut.
Thank you, Ms. Williams.
I'm tired of seeing all these young boys
with sloppy hair
and pants around their knees.
- A man wears his pants around his waist.
- Yes, ma'am.
Well, tell your mama I said hello.
And I'll see you next week.
- Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Ms. Williams?
That's me.
You must be Elizabeth.
Well, it's so good to meet you.
You can call me Clara.
Well, come on in.
Let me show you the house.
I got to put my coffee pot on.
Can I get you something?
Oh, no, thank you. I had mine at home.
This is a beautiful house.
I think so, too.
Built in 1905.
And I've lived here almost 50 years.
Leo added that sun porch on the back
all by himself.
Oh, this must be Leo.
That's Leo.
We were married for 14
years before he died.
He had just been promoted to captain
before that picture was taken.
He was so handsome in that uniform.
He's fine, ain't he?
Yes, we wanted five or six children,
but the Lord only gave us Clyde,
'cause he was all I could handle.
You see that big crack
over there on the wall?
That was Clyde.
Now, this is my third favorite place.
It's my sitting room.
- Hmm. What do you do in here?
- Mainly sit.
Well, come on in here.
Let me show you the dining room.
Now this is my second favorite place.
I love this room.
This is beautiful.
And I love this fireplace.
I've got a lot of good memories in here.
Yes, I do.
Lot of laughter.
And a few tears, too.
Now this is why I'm moving in with Clyde
a few blocks away. Ooh!
It's getting harder to
negotiate these stairs.
Okay, so three bedrooms and two full baths.
- Do you mind if I take some pictures?
- Oh, go ahead, that's fine.
Oh, you got one of those smart phones.
I've been meaning to get me one of those.
Can't do nothing with my phone
but call folks.
Must be a dumb phone.
- You got it?
- I do.
They say if you live in a house
with stairs, you'll live longer.
So I should make it to 180.
This is fascinating, Ms. Clara.
Oh, that's my Wall of Remembrance.
And when things aren't going so well,
I look back on it,
and I'm reminded that God
is still in control.
It encourages me.
I sure could use some of that.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Okay. So, I've got
a few questions about utilities,
and then we should probably talk
about the asking price.
All right.
Okay. So, I think I got everything
that I need for now.
So nice to meet you, Ms. Clara.
Listen, if you're available tomorrow,
I'd like to come by and show you
some comparisons in the area.
Well, why don't you come by for coffee
tomorrow morning
and we'll talk about it then? Say 10:00?
Ah. Okay. Yeah, I can do that.
I'll see you at 10:00.
By the way, what's your most favorite room?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Then I look forward to tomorrow.
Mmm-hmm.
How you doing?
- Mr. Jordan?
- Yes.
- Samples closet?
- Yes, please.
- Right this way.
- All right.
You can just use the third shelf down
and just leave the door open,
- and I'll come back and get it later.
- All right. Thank you.
You must be Mr. Jordan.
Dr. Morris, yes. I'm Tony Jordan,
Brightwell Pharmaceuticals.
We met last March.
- I remember. How are you?
- I'm doing fine.
I saw your write-up on new stimulants
and you showed interest in Predizim.
So I just left you a case
in your samples closet.
Oh, that's fantastic. I appreciate that.
Oh, it's no problem.
You'll easily find them.
It's the third shelf, blue caps.
Now what I need you to do though,
is just sign this receipt.
And it just shows that
I left them with you.
Now, Dr. Morris, if you need any more,
you just let me know
and I'll be glad to bring some over.
Thank you, Tony. We'll try them out.
All right. Sounds good.
We'll see you again.
Right.
And I'll be looking forward
to that next article.
Thank you.
And he thinks
it's my sister's fault.
Can you even believe that?
Well, if my man said that to me,
I'd be angry, too.
We don't fight that much anymore.
After 31 years of stalemates, girl,
it just is not worth it.
Oh, I wouldn't put up with it.
His money became your money
the minute he said, "I do."
So I'd give it to my sister anyway.
I don't even like my sister.
Just be careful, Elizabeth.
You do not want World War Ill
to break out in your home.
No. No, I don't.
But there are days, Mandy. There are days.
It's hard to submit to a man like that.
You know what my mama used to say to me?
She used to say that sometimes submission
is learning to duck
so God can hit your husband.
Hmm. It's tough being a woman.
You got that right.
Veronica, this is Tony Jordan.
We met a few days ago
after I met with Mr. Barnes.
Hey, listen, uh, I'll be coming
through town next week
and I was wondering if you could
recommend a couple of nice restaurants.
Feel free to call me back at this number.
Take care.
I appreciate you coming
this morning.
Coffee will be ready
in a couple of minutes.
Oh, sounds good.
I ran a sales report from the area.
I wrote down a suggested asking price
for the house.
Mmm-hmm.
Well, what do you think?
Now, what did you say
your husband did for a living?
Um, well, we actually haven't talked
about that,
but he's a sales rep
for Brightwell Pharmaceuticals.
Mmm-hmm.
And where did you say you attended church?
Well, we occasionally attend
Riverdale Community.
Mmm-hmm.
So you would say you know the Lord.
Yes! I would say I know the Lord.
You think the Lord is okay
with this asking price?
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
And you have children?
Ms. Clara, my husband, Tony, and I
have been married for 16 years.
We have one daughter.
Her name is Danielle and she's 10.
She enjoys pop music and ice cream
and jumping rope.
Oh. Well, that's good to know.
Now, you say
you attend church occasionally.
Is that because your pastor
only preaches occasionally?
Ms. Clara, I really would like to help you
sell your house.
That's why I'm here.
As far as my faith is concerned,
I believe in God, just like most people.
He's very important to me.
Mmm-hmm. Well, let me get our coffee.
So, if I asked you
what your prayer life was like,
would you say that it was hot or cold?
I don't know that I would say it's hot.
I mean, we're like most people.
We have full schedules. We work.
But I would consider myself
a spiritual person.
I'm not hot, but I'm not cold either.
Just, you know, somewhere in the middle.
Here you go.
- I've got cream or sugar if you need it.
- Oh, no, thank you. I like it black.
Ms. Clara, you like your coffee
room temperature?
No, baby, mine's hot.
Elizabeth,
people drink their coffee hot or cold,
but nobody likes it lukewarm,
not even the Lord.
Point taken, Ms. Clara.
But why do you feel the need
to examine my personal life?
Because I've been where you are.
And you don't have to step
on the same land mines that I did.
That's a waste of time.
And this asking price is just fine.
Let me get you a hot cup of coffee.
I was a little sneaky last time.
What land mines do you think
I might step on?
You tell me.
Now, if there was one thing in your life
that you could make better,
what would it be?
Just one?
Well, I'd probably have to say my marriage.
If there's one thing we
do well, it's fight.
No, I don't think you do.
I'm sorry?
Just because you argue a lot
doesn't mean that you fight well.
Every couple has some friction
every now and then.
But I bet that you never
feel like you've won
after you've had an argument
with your husband.
Can I ask you how much
you pray for your husband?
Uh...
Well, very little.
Elizabeth,
I think it's time for me to show you
my favorite place in this house.
Now, this is where I do my fighting.
A closet?
I call it my war room.
So...
So, you wrote prayers
for each area of your life?
A prayer strategy. Yes.
Now, I used to do
what you and your husband are doing,
but it got me nowhere.
And then I really started studying
what the scriptures say.
And God showed me that it wasn't my job
to do the heavy lifting. No.
That was something that only He could do.
It was my job to seek Him, to trust Him
and to stand on His word.
Ms. Clara, I've never
seen anything like this.
And I admire it, I really do. I just...
I don't have time to pray
that much every day.
But you apparently have time
to fight losing battles with your husband.
Elizabeth,
if you will give me one hour a week,
I can teach you how to fight the right way
with the right weapons.
Since you're good with the asking price,
I'll go ahead and list the house.
I'd, uh...
Like to think about our other discussion.
Elizabeth, please forgive me
for being so direct,
but I see in you a warrior
that needs to be awakened.
But I will respect
whatever decision you make.
Thank you, Ms. Clara.
I hope you have a good day.
You, too.
Don't let me push too hard, Lord.
I know I got a big mouth.
If they do that stunt
in the competition, they'll win.
Why don't you ask your dad
about helping us get uniforms?
He's not here.
It's not like he would care anyway.
Can you ask your mom?
My mom already gave part of the money.
Come on, we can go to my room.
So, I told my dad
that he could jump with us,
and he totally started laughing.
He said he would only do it
if Mom did it with him,
which, of course, she would never do.
So, they, like, start talking
about doing the worst routine ever.
Like, in a funny way.
And she starts laughing so hard,
her face turned bright red.
Then she starts squeaking
'cause she couldn't breathe.
It was hilarious.
I wish I lived at your house.
Whenever my parents are together,
they just fight.
Jennifer, how's your family?
Fine.
Would you like to stay for dinner?
You're welcome to eat with us.
Okay.
Okay, well, I'm gonna go change.
I'll call you girls down in a few minutes.
Danielle...
You know we love you, right?
That wasn't very convincing.
Well, I think you love me a little bit.
A little bit?
Danielle, you're my daughter.
You're the most important thing
in the whole world to me.
You gotta believe that.
What's my team name?
Urn...
The Firecrackers.
That was last year.
What are our colors?
What jump rope tricks
did I just learn to do?
Who's my new coach?
What award did I win last week on my team?
You won an award last week?
Danielle, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Well, good morning.
Her heart is just breaking
and I was completely unaware.
Tony, he's completely unaware.
That man is running out of time, Ms. Clara.
He's off in his own world
being top salesman somewhere
while his daughter is growing
more and more calloused to him every day.
He shows no interest in
anybody but himself.
And another thing. I don't
have proof of this,
but if he's not getting it from me,
he's got to be getting it from somebody.
He makes all these little flirtatious
comments to other women...
Uh, uh, uh. Elizabeth, just so I know,
how much of the one hour
we got together today
are you gonna spend
whining about your husband?
And how much we gonna spend
on what the Lord can do about it?
I'm sorry, Ms. Clara. I just get so
wound up the more I think about it.
Your thoughts about your husband
are almost entirely negative, aren't they?
He acts like an enemy to me.
See, you're fighting the wrong enemy.
Now, your husband certainly has his issues,
but he's not your enemy.
When I fought against my husband,
I was fighting against my own marriage
and my family.
Now, I tried for years to fix Leo,
but I couldn't do it.
Well, I haven't got anywhere with Tony.
'Cause it's not your job.
Who said that it was your responsibility
to fix Tony?
It's your job to love him, to respect him
and to pray for the man.
God knows he needs it.
And men don't like it when
their woman's always trying to fix them.
Elizabeth,
you got to plead with God
so that He can do what only He can do.
And then you got to get out of the way
and let Him do it!
I don't even know where to start.
Here.
You will find some of my
favorite scriptures in here.
They were my battle plan
to pray for my family.
You can start with that.
Mmm, hey, hey, hey.
Said you been bound up.
Lookin' for a way to break free.
Devil's had you tied up.
Listen to these words from me.
Your situation may seem hopeless.
- But it's not the end.
- Oh, yeah.
Though you are burdened
and have shackles on your feet.
Now, I want you to know
You're about to break loose.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jesus took the keys and gave 'em to you.
So here's what you gotta do.
Shake loose
Everything that binds you up.
Who told you.
Who told you that you can't make it.
When God says that you can shake it
Shake loose.
Everything that binds you up.
- Praise Him like it's your last chance.
- Get up and do the David dance.
Shake yourself loose.
Mom?
I'm in here, Danielle.
Mom, are you okay?
Yes. What do you need?
Why are you eating chips in the closet?
I'm just having some private time. Okay?
Okay.
Um, Jennifer wanted to know
if I could spend the night.
I already did my chores,
and it's okay with her parents.
Okay, but I want you home
by lunch tomorrow. Okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
- And, Danielle,
don't tell anybody
I was eating chips in this closet.
Don't tell anyone my mom
was eating chips in the closet, okay?
- Who are you talking to?
- Jennifer.
Jennifer?
Yes, ma'am?
I'm asking you not to tell anybody
I was eating chips in my closet.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
What's that smell?
That would be my shoes, Jennifer.
And if you girls would kindly shut the
door, you won't have to smell it anymore.
Is she not allowed to eat chips?
I can have all the chips I want!
This is my house!
Great.
Hello, Tony. How are you?
- Julia, how're you doing?
- I'm doing well, thanks.
- Having a good day?
- I am, thank you.
Um, Coleman's expecting you
and Tom's in there, too.
Thanks for the heads up.
You're welcome. Right this way.
- All right, thank you.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Tony! How's my favorite rep?
- Real good. How're you doing?
- Heard we got the Holcombe account.
- Yes, we did.
- That's fantastic. You did it again.
- Appreciate that. Thank you.
Even Tom was impressed,
and you know that's hard to do.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
Look, I know you're on your way home,
but we just wanted to say thanks.
And you got a nice bonus check
coming your way.
- I like that.
- Yeah, you do.
- How's Elizabeth?
- She's good.
- Tell her I said hello.
- I'll do it.
- Good to see you.
- All right.
Cynthia, it's not gonna do you
any good to fight about it.
You can't get the job for him.
Well, is he trying at all?
Is he sending out resumes
or making calls, anything?
I know.
Well, I'm sorry, but he's making it hard,
not just on you but everybody around you.
No, I'm not saying that
we're not gonna help.
We're still talking about it.
Okay?
Listen, Tony just got home.
I need to call you later.
Yeah. I love you, too. Bye.
- How was your trip?
- It was good.
- I take it that was your sister.
- Yep.
Darren getting a job?
Not yet.
Not yet as in he's trying?
Or not yet as in he's still sitting
on the couch playing video games?
Tony, what he does is not Cynthia's fault.
Listen, she just needs one month's rent
and a car payment.
I think we should at least do that.
Cynthia married a loser. Okay?
That was her choice
when everybody told her not to.
- It is her fault.
- Tony, she cannot control him.
She's got a job, but it's not enough.
Listen, I'm not asking for $5,000 anymore.
I'm asking for one month's rent
and a car payment.
And the next month
you'll be asking for the same thing, Liz.
So the answer is still no.
And what is that smell in here?
I'm putting powder in my shoes.
- Well, can't you do that outside?
- Yes.
Tony, if you won't do it for her,
do it for me.
No.
- You got another bonus?
- Yes, sir.
Dude, I went in the wrong line of work.
Well, I couldn't have been a paramedic.
- You got that right, bro.
- And you too calm to be a salesman.
Yeah.
Yeah, but could you imagine
if I got bonuses
every time I saved somebody's life?
Ohhh! Check it out. Heimlich, $200.
Right? Um, CPR, $400.
Right.
Like $1,000, if they're ugly.
Dude, you remember that one lady who had
swallowed that garlic and she choked,
and I had to give her mouth-to-mouth?
- Yeah.
- That should've been a Hawaiian vacation.
- I couldn't have done it.
- Yeah. You could do it.
You're not gonna let somebody die
in front of you while you eat your salad.
I don't do CPR, Mike. I'd
have just called 911.
That's just cold.
You just gonna let somebody die?
Yo, what if it was your wife?
Hold on, brother. What? What's that?
- What is that?
- What's what?
Dude, what's up with you and Liz?
Nothing.
Nothing? Look at you getting all uptight.
You got extra veins popping out
that wasn't even there before.
Mike, I'm just tired of her. Okay?
All right? I said it.
- I'm just tired of her junk.
- Her junk?
Dude, you married her, junk and all.
It's not some sort of buffet where you
get to pick and choose what you want.
You get all of her, bro.
And you better not have somebody
on the side.
So, you're trying to do CPR
on my personal life now?
Okay. Yeah, I'm a paramedic.
But I'm also a Christian,
which means I help people
while I'm helping people.
Mike, look, we've been friends
for a long time,
but some things
are just none of your business.
True, and since we've been friends
a long time,
I'm not just gonna watch your marriage die.
So if it's bleeding,
I'm not gonna keep eating my salad.
I'll see you in church.
I'd like to see the church in you, bro.
Hey, somebody need to come move this.
This was a treat for me, Elizabeth.
I enjoy coming here.
And your daughter is precious.
She is.
You know, there are days
I wish she had a brother or sister.
We were just too busy chasing our careers.
I don't know that that
was a wise thing to do.
You don't enjoy your job?
Oh, there are days I do. Sold a house
this morning, so that was good.
I'd just rather have a good marriage
than more money.
Mom! Can we go get ice cream?
They sell it right over there.
Ms. Clara, would you like some ice cream?
I'll tell you what.
If you go get the ice cream
and let your mother walk me to the car,
- I'll pay for it.
- Oh, no, no, no. I'm paying for it.
And rob me of a blessing?
I'm paying, we're all eating.
And I'll take two scoops
of Butter Pecan, please. In a cup.
I'll have one scoop
of Cookies and Cream, okay?
And listen, just stay right there,
'cause we're gonna pull the car around
and pick you up at the entrance.
Okay. Can I have strawberry sherbet with
gummy worms and chocolate syrup on top?
Ugh!
So, what does a normal week
in your life look like?
Well, my son drops in for an hour or two
during the week.
I go grocery shopping,
an occasional doctor's visit,
and my girlfriends and I get together
on Friday afternoons for coffee.
Other than that, I read a lot
and I spend time with Jesus.
I used to spend so much time
with my girlfriends before my job...
Give me your money right now.
Did you hear me?
Both of you, give it to me now.
Okay. Okay, we will.
Just please, put the knife down.
Do it, and do it now!
No.
Now you put that knife down right now
in the name of Jesus.
And you believe he was early 20s?
Yeah. Maybe 25.
So, let me get this straight.
He was pointing a knife at you
and you told him to put it down
in Jesus' name?
Right. Now when you write that down,
don't leave out Jesus.
People always leaving Jesus out.
That's one of the reasons
we're in the mess we in.
Yes, ma'am.
You know, what concerns me
is that you could've easily been killed.
Well, I know a lot of people probably
would've given him their money.
I understand that, but
that's their decision.
Are you not eating your
ice cream, Elizabeth?
No. I'm not hungry anymore.
Well, let me help you with that. No
reason to waste perfectly good ice cream.
Mmm!
Oh, oh, oh! Now that's good! Mmm-hmm.
I'm sorry, I just thought
I should call Tony.
I understand.
You'd think he'd be more alarmed.
He just kept saying
that since we were all okay,
I should just calm down.
I'm having trouble
calming down myself.
Really? You seemed calm earlier.
Yeah, but I got a huge sugar-rush
from all that ice cream.
I feel like I can run around
the block a few times.
Oh. Uh...
While we on the subject of Tony,
I have something for you to do.
What's that?
I want you to write down everything
that you can think of that he's done wrong.
Ms. Clara, if I did that,
I'd be writing a long time.
Well, then just write down the highlights.
And I'll be back to check on you
in a little while.
Well, that's almost three pages.
And I could write more, but you'll
get the gist of it when you read it.
Actually, I'm not gonna read it.
My question to you is this.
In light of all these wrongs,
does God still love Tony?
We both know he does.
Do you?
Now, Ms. Clara, you're meddling.
There's love in my heart for Tony, but it's
just buried under a lot of frustration.
- So he needs grace.
- Grace?
I don't know that he deserves grace.
Do you deserve grace?
Ms. Clara, you have a habit of backing
me up in a corner and making me squirm.
I felt the same way.
But the question still remains.
Do you deserve grace?
The Bible says that no one is righteous,
not even one.
For we have all sinned.
So, really, none of us deserve grace.
But we all still want God's forgiveness.
Elizabeth, it comes down to this.
Jesus shed his blood on the cross.
He died for you.
Even when you did not deserve it.
And He rose from the grave
and offers forgiveness and salvation
for anyone who turns to Him.
But the Bible also says
that we can't ask Him to forgive us
while refusing to forgive others.
I know, Ms. Clara.
But that's just so hard to do.
Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
But that's where grace comes in!
He gives us grace!
And He helps us to give it to others,
even when they don't deserve it.
We all deserve judgment.
And that is what a holy God gives us when
we don't repent and believe in His Son.
I had to forgive Leo for some things,
and it wasn't easy.
But it freed me.
Elizabeth, there's not room for you
and God on the throne of your heart.
It's either Him or it's you.
You need to step down.
Now, if you want victory,
you're gonna have to first surrender.
But, Ms. Clara,
do I just back off and choose to forgive
and then just let him walk all over me?
God is a good defense attorney.
Trust it to Him.
And then you can turn your focus
to the real enemy.
The real enemy?
The one that wants to remain hidden.
The one that wants to distract you
and deceive you and divide you
from the Lord and your husband!
You see, that's how he works.
Satan comes to steal, kill and destroy.
And he is stealing your joy.
He is killing your faith
and he's trying to destroy your family.
If I were you,
I would get my heart right with God.
And you need to do your fighting in prayer!
And you need to kick the real enemy
out of your home with the word of God.
It's time for you to fight, Elizabeth.
It's time for you to
fight for your marriage!
It's time for you to fight the real enemy!
It's time for you
to take off the gloves and do it!
There's no magic in the location you pray.
But scripture does say to go
into your inner room and pray in secret.
And your heavenly Father, who sees
what's done in secret, will reward you.
Now get rid of any distractions
and focus your heart and mind on Him.
Acknowledge that He is God,
and that you desperately need Him.
Now, be grateful for your blessings,
but lift your needs and requests to Him.
If you've got something to confess,
then confess it.
Ask Him for forgiveness.
Then choose to believe Him
when He says that He loves you
and will take care of you.
Then pray for the heart of your husband,
your daughter and anyone else
that the Lord brings to your mind.
And don't rush it.
You take your time, and then you listen.
God...
God, I need you.
I know I haven't prayed like I should.
I know that I haven't...
I haven't followed you like I should.
But I need you, right now.
Lord, I've been so angry at Tony,
and I'm still so angry at him.
But I don't want to lose my marriage.
Lord, forgive me.
Forgive me.
I'm not his judge, you are.
But I'm asking you, please,
please don't let him do this.
Take over.
Please, take over.
Take my heart and take all this anger.
Help him love me again.
And help me love him.
If he's doing something wrong,
don't let him get away with it.
Stand in his way.
I'm asking you, please,
to help me.
"The thief comes only to steal"
"to kill and destroy."
"But I've come that you may have a life,
and have it abundantly."
"But the Lord is faithful."
"He will strengthen
and protect you from the evil one."
"Submit to God."
"Resist the devil,"
"and he will flee."
"Submit to God."
"Resist the devil, and he will flee."
"Resist the devil,"
"and he will flee."
I don't know where you are, Devil,
but I know you can hear me.
You have played with my mind
and had your way long enough.
No more.
You are done!
Jesus is the Lord of this house.
And that means there's no place
for you here anymore.
So take your lies, your schemes
and your accusations,
and get out in Jesus' name!
You can't have my marriage.
You can't have my daughter.
And you sure can't have my man.
This house is under new management
and that means you are out!
And another thing.
I am so sick of you stealing my joy,
but that's changing, too.
My joy doesn't come from my friends.
It doesn't come from my job.
It doesn't even come from my husband.
My joy is found in Jesus.
And just in case you forgot,
he has already defeated you.
So go back to Hell where you belong
and leave my family alone.
You know what I'd really like right now?
Tell me.
A glass of my favorite wine.
Okay, we can do that. What is it?
It's not here.
It's at my apartment.
Well, if it's your favorite,
I'd like to try it.
Here you are, sir.
Hope you both have a wonderful evening.
Thank you. We will.
Veronica, listen.
I need a minute. All right?
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Mom?
Danielle?
What happened to your closet?
I'm doing something
I should've done a long time ago.
I'm learning how to pray
and fight
and trust.
By cleaning out your closet?
No. Well, yes. But no.
I mean, it needed to be cleaned out.
But that's not why I did it. I did it...
I did it to fight in prayer.
You're fighting God?
No, I'm not...
Well, sometimes I do fight God.
But I shouldn't 'cause He always wins.
So, you know, I'm praying
for God to fight for me
'cause I am just sick of losing.
But not against God.
I need to lose against God.
I'm sick of losing in other areas
where I'm just fighting
but I just keep losing all the time.
It's exhausting.
So I'm learning how not to fight God
and how to let Him fight for me
so that we can all win.
Does that make any sense?
No.
You know what?
I don't make much sense when I'm tired.
You must be really tired.
Let's just go get a late night snack. Okay?
And I'll try it again.
Okay.
How many storms have I been through.
How many led me right to You.
You're using the pain, the hardest days.
For my good, my good.
So what do I fear
God, You are with me.
Guiding my steps today.
Through the mountains, valleys
sun and rain.
Lord, lead the way Lead the way.
I will follow, I will press on.
Even when the walk feels long.
Your hands hold me together
Your love is with me forever...
Now see, you're already influencing
your daughter.
This can change everything for her.
I admit, when I first started praying in
there, 10 minutes seemed like an eternity.
Now I have a hard time
even wanting to leave.
One step in front of the other.
I'm gonna press on, press on.
Oh. Hello.
Whoa. Urn...
I just need you to sign for this package.
Oh. Thank you so much.
This is a present for my daughter.
I can't wait to give it to her.
Well, I hope it takes your breath away.
Have a nice day, ma'am.
- I like it. And you got one, too?
- Yep, I sure did.
And you can write your prayer requests
in there, your favorite verses.
- We can journal, anything we want.
- Hey, Daddy.
- Hey, Danielle.
- Hey.
I didn't think you were coming home
till tonight.
Yeah. I finished up everything
pretty early, so...
- You got enough for me?
- Sure.
Jennifer's mom is coming
to pick Danielle up in a few minutes,
- but you and I can eat.
- All right.
- I'll take my stuff to the room.
- Hey, how are you?
- I'm good. How are you?
You and the girls
hanging out today?
Yeah. We're gonna go
to the park for a couple hours,
and then I thought we could grab
a milkshake at Chick-fil-A's,
if that's okay?
So, what's been going on here?
Oh. Well, I sold another house on Tuesday.
And I already told you
about getting held up, so...
Yeah, look, about that.
It's not that I didn't care.
I just got really busy,
so when I saw that you were all right...
I understand. It's all right. I'm sorry
for getting so worked up about it.
You're sorry?
Yeah. I knew you were at work,
probably in a meeting.
I should've just waited
till later to bring it up.
My mind was just racing,
so I took it out on you.
But you know what?
I really think it was good for Danielle.
I think it helped her to realize how important
it is to be aware of who's around you, so...
You want hot sauce?
- Yeah, that's fine.
- You want mild or Wrath of God?
I don't want Wrath of God.
Let me have the other one.
What do you want, Liz?
- You mean, right now?
- Yeah.
Well, I would kill for
a hot fudge sundae.
Just
fudge everywhere.
And two scoops of ice cream,
Cookies and Cream.
Whipped cream. Just mounds,
mounds of whipped cream on top.
And one cherry. One cherry.
And my feet are killing me.
Man, I would love a foot rub.
Liz, I'm not rubbing your feet.
Okay.
Well, you wanna pray?
Yeah.
God, we thank you for this food.
And we thank you
for taking care of our family.
- Amen.
I'm starving. Let's eat.
Mmm. It's good.
And you double checked your numbers.
Twice.
Tony's inventory is off, Rick.
We saw the same thing last week
when he left Asheville.
He may just be padding numbers,
but there's a pattern here.
You're the district manager.
You gotta cal! This in.
- Yeah. Thanks, Greg.
- Sorry, man. Later.
Why, Tony?
Hey, Danielle. Where's Daddy?
He left.
He got a call from his boss and had to go.
- From Rick?
- I think so.
- Did he say when he'd be back?
- No, ma'am.
Oh, I hear him.
Hey.
Tony?
First off,
I don't want any grief from you. Okay?
'Cause I'm really not in the mood
to talk about this right now.
Tony, what's going on?
I just lost my job!
Okay. So, we'll just do what we gotta do.
What, no sarcastic comment?
Tony, I think we'll be fine.
Liz, you heard me, right? I just got fired!
Okay? So that means no income.
No company car. No health coverage.
We can't even afford this house anymore.
I understand.
Listen, I'll just pick up some new properties
while you look for a different job. Okay?
So, that's it?
You just gonna roll with it?
What else am I supposed to do?
Sometimes I don't get you, Liz.
I'll go start dinner.
Tony!
Please help me! Please!
Tony, help me, please!
Tony!
Tony, no! No!
Danielle, have you seen my gym bag?
No, sir.
" Lord, I pray for Tony,
that you would turn his heart back to you."
"Help me to love him,
and give him a fresh love for me."
"I surrender my rights to you as Lord"
"and ask you to bless him as he honors you
and to expose him if he walks in deceit."
"Build him up as the man
you intend him to be."
"Help me to support and respect him.
I ask for your help to love him."
"In Jesus' name I pray."
Daddy?
I found your gym bag
next to the washing machine.
Okay. You can just set it
right there, Danielle.
Hey, Danielle.
When did Mama do this to her closet?
Hmm, a few weeks ago.
- So, the whole closet was empty?
- Yeah, except the papers on the wall.
And what did she do with her clothes?
Mike, I don't know, man. Some other closet.
What does that matter?
Dude, I don't think you understand
how important this is.
When was the last time you heard
of a woman giving up some closet space?
All I know is, you can fight against
your wife and probably hold your own.
But if God is fighting for her,
you can hit the gym all you want to, bro.
It's not looking good for you.
Man!
I wish my wife would pray for me like that.
Plus, I could use the closet space.
All right, man, you good, yo.
I'm about to bounce.
- See you later, bro.
- All right.
Excuse me.
Can you tell Danielle
I'll be back to get her after practice?
- Sure, I'll tell her.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Tony! Please help me! Please!
Jesus,
I'm not a good man.
I'm selfish.
I'm prideful.
And I'm hurting this family.
But this, this is not who I wanted to be.
I don't like the man I've become,
but I don't know how to fix it.
I don't know what to do.
Forgive me, please.
Forgive me, Jesus.
One, two, three, go.
Left, left, right.
Yes! Go!
One, two, three.
Left, left, right.
Hey, you know what?
I thought your jump roping routine
was gonna be something simple.
But it wasn't. It's pretty difficult.
But you were really good, Danielle.
I mean, I was impressed.
You're really good.
Thanks.
Daddy, why are they here?
They've come to
get this car, Danielle.
Excuse me.
- Rick.
- Tony.
I'm sorry about this.
It's not your fault, Rick.
Listen, I need you to sign
that we came for the car.
And clean out any items that belong to you.
Yep.
Already did.
You're a talented guy, Tony.
I was sorry to see this happen.
- You take care.
- Yeah.
Why are they taking Daddy's car?
We'll talk about it later, baby, okay?
Listen, why don't you go inside
and knock out some chores
before lunch, all right'? Okay.
I picked up a couple more houses
to sell this morning.
Asked Mandy to give me everything
she could for the next couple months.
That's good, Liz.
Can we talk?
Sure.
I just don't understand
why you treat me this way.
When I told you what happened with my job,
I expected you to hit the ceiling, Liz.
So, in my mind, I was
ready to defend myself.
Except this time, I can't.
And I hate saying this...
But I deserved to get fired.
I was deceiving them.
And I was deceiving you.
I almost cheated on you, Liz.
I thought about it.
I almost did it.
But you know all this.
And you're still here.
Then I see your closet,
and the way you praying for me.
Why would you do that
when you see the type of man I've become?
'Cause I'm not done with us.
I will fight for our marriage.
But I've learned that my contentment
can't come from you.
Tony, I love you.
But I am His before I'm yours.
And because I love Jesus,
I'm staying right here.
I'm sorry, Liz.
I asked God to forgive me,
but I need you to forgive me.
I don't want you to quit on me, Liz.
I will.
I forgive you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Lord.
And this just happened now?
He did?
Well, what'd he say?
Oh, sweet Jesus. Oh, Lord!
Oh. Oh!
See, I told you, Elizabeth.
I told you that God would fight for you.
Oh, Jesus!
All right, baby, I'll talk to you soon.
Om.
Devil, you just got your butt kicked!
My God is faithful.
And my God is powerful.
And my God is in charge.
You can't fire Him and He'll never retire!
Thank you, Jesus. Glory Hallelujah!
My God is good.
My God is good, and He's faithful.
Hey, Danielle.
Hey, Daddy.
Listen, I need to tell you something.
I don't think I've been
a very good dad to you.
And I haven't been very loving
to your mother either.
Urn...
I can do better, Danielle.
You both deserve better from me.
But you know what?
I've asked God to help me.
And
I wanted to ask you
if you would forgive me
and give me another chance.
Think you can do that?
Listen, I do love you, Danielle.
I love you too, Daddy.
We're sorry. You have reached
a number that has been disconnected
or is no longer in service.
Slow down, I'm old. You know, I'm old now.
Okay, here we go.
Okay! I'm in there!
- Keep going!
- You got it!
Okay. I'm trying! My knees!
Here we go. Got the turn.
What's the other move, Danielle?
Okay, wait.
- Good grief!
- Daddy, why don't you jump with us?
Yeah, that would be awesome!
No, no. I don't think
they let parents do that.
Yeah, they do. But no parents
do 'cause they can't keep up.
- Oh, really?
- Dad, it's an open league.
You can jump in the freestyle competition.
They'll let you.
Look, tell you what.
Let me think about it, okay?
Okay, I'll think about it. All right?
Now if I'm gonna do it, I wanna do
it right. So let's try it again.
Get it going. Get it going for me.
Okay, here we go. Here we go. Okay. Okay.
All right, here we go. Turn. And we turn...
Tony?
Tony, what are you doing?
I'm struggling-
With What?
What is this?
It was my bonus plan.
Where did you get these?
I've been keeping some for myself
each time I take samples to a client.
I thought they had to sign
for what you gave them.
There's ways around that, Liz.
Tony, you gotta take these back.
Liz, I could be prosecuted for this.
Look, I've already lost my job.
So, now I'm supposed to go and tell
Danielle her daddy might be going to jail?
Then why are you struggling?
What you have there
is fourth-quarter projections.
Now, if anything's off on that, don't...
Coleman, Tony Jordan's here to see you.
- Do you know what he wants?
- He didn't say.
Just said he wants five
minutes of your time.
Tony? Coleman's waiting for you
in the conference room.
Thank you.
Hello, Tony.
Coleman. Tom.
Look, I appreciate you
guys meeting with me.
I just need to bring you something back
that belongs to the company,
and apologize for taking it.
What's in the box?
You weren't just padding your numbers,
you were stealing samples
and selling them. Is that right?
Let me get this straight.
We give you a high salary
with awards and benefits and trips,
and you decide to thank us
by taking even more for yourself?
Do you realize
we could have you prosecuted for this?
Tom.
Why would you bring this in now?
Because I needed to confess what I've done
and ask for your forgiveness.
Forgiveness?
I mean, how long have you been doing this?
How much money did you make?
About $19,000.
19,000?
- Is that all? Really?
- Tom.
Tony, it doesn't make sense
that you would do this
after you've already been terminated.
I realize that.
But I've gotten right with my family.
I've gotten right with God.
But I need to get right with you.
So I'm ready to accept
whatever decision you make.
Including arrest?
Whatever the consequence.
Oh.
That makes it easier for us.
Coleman, it's time to
call the authorities.
Not yet.
Tony, are you willing to sign a statement?
I am.
Then I want two days to think about it.
- Two days?
- Yes.
You'll hear from me by then.
Thank you.
Hey, girls. Why don't you go inside
and grab something cold to drink?
Okay? We can start back in a little bit.
- Okay. Thanks, Ms. Jordan.
- All right.
Hey. Hey.
Well?
I don't know.
I mean, Tom just wanted
to throw me in jail.
But Coleman says he wants two days
to think about it.
- Really? Did he seem angry?
- I couldn't tell.
Liz, this was the most awkward thing
I've ever done.
Yeah, but you did it.
Listen, you did the right thing.
Now we just have to pray and wait.
Hey, why don't you go change?
Just come practice with your daughter.
Liz, why should I practice for a
competition when I might be in jail?
You don't know that.
Whatever happens, we trust God, right?
Right.
This is crazy. You know that, right?
But it's gonna take.
Crazy faith.
So what if it costs everything.
I'm stepping out
I'm taking the leap.
And it's gonna take.
Crazy faith.
So what if it costs me everything.
I'm stepping out.
I'm taking the leap of crazy faith.
Crazy faith.
You're nervous.
Trying not to think about it.
What time are you supposed to be there?
9200.
- Coleman?
- Hello, Tony.
- Hi, Elizabeth.
- Hi, Coleman. How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
I know this is unexpected, but I wondered
if you might give me a few minutes to talk.
- Yeah, sure. Come on in.
- Thank you.
Tony, I've been thinking about your visit.
It's probably all I've thought about
the past two days.
What you did was wrong.
And I was disappointed.
But we've fired salesmen before,
and well, life goes on.
But then you showed back up.
And, Tony, I've never seen anybody do
what you did.
I've never seen a man take total
responsibility for his wrongdoing,
no matter the consequence.
And I kept asking myself, why?
Why would you do that?
The only answer I can come up with
is that you were sincere
in your desire to make it right,
and that you regret what you've done.
So I've chosen to believe you.
I can't give you your job back,
but I've decided not to prosecute.
I do think it would be appropriate
to return the $19,000 back to the company.
- Yeah, we've already decided to do that.
- Very good.
Well, if you'll sign an agreement
to that effect,
I think we should all move on.
So if you don't mind me seeing myself out,
I'll give you your evening back.
- Thank you, Tony.
- Thank you.
- Elizabeth.
Tony, that was grace!
That was God's grace toward us.
Thank you, Jesus.
I just love these old houses.
They have so much character.
Oh, yeah. I agree.
Well, the master bath was updated recently,
but she kept the original tub.
And all the tiles are brand new.
And, you know, I think this is best of all,
the floor is original hardwoods.
- I love hardwood floors.
- And you know what I found?
The neighborhood is so great
because it's established.
And quiet, you know? It seems mature.
How long have you guys been in ministry?
Uh, Charles pastored
the same church
- for 35 years.
- Wow.
But, you know, we loved it,
but we knew it was time for a change,
and we wanted to be near our kids
and grand kids to help mentor them.
Charles, what are you doing?
Someone's been praying in this closet.
That's right. That was her prayer closet.
How did you know that?
It's almost like it's baked in.
Ma'am, we'll take the house.
Well, hello. Come on in.
You must be Elizabeth.
- Yes, thank you.
- Hey, there, young lady.
- You're C.W. Williams, the city manager.
- I am.
- You're Clyde?
- I'm Clyde.
- You got to be kidding me.
- Hey, Elizabeth!
- Hey, Danielle!
- Nice to meet you.
I'll let you all catch up.
You never told me that your son
was the city manager!
I didn't? My son's the city manager.
Okay.
I got some good news for you.
I bet you gonna tell me
that a retired pastor from Texas
and his wife wanna buy my house.
Now see,
see, that's the kind of relationship
with God I want.
I want Him speaking to me like that.
What did He say?
Well, it was actually your daughter.
She texted me on my new smart phone
on the way over here.
Don't be mad, Mom!
I hardly get to text anybody!
And this thing is so handy.
I've already downloaded
a couple prayer apps,
and got a couple gospel songs.
All right, guys.
Wanna take these popsicles outside,
eat them on the back porch?
Here we go. Two hot cups of coffee.
Well, if it's hot, then I'll drink it.
Now, we're still gonna get together
for our little chats, right?
Oh, yes!
- But now it can't just be the both of us.
- What do you mean?
Oh, you need to find a young woman
to invest in, and I'll do the same.
We all need help every now and then.
Ms. Clara, I really can't tell you
how much your friendship means to me.
Oh, that goes for the both of us.
No, really. I wasn't willing to admit
how much help I needed.
And I needed somebody to wake me up
from the insanity of doing
the same thing over and over.
You've been a gift from God to me.
Don't you think that
this has been one-sided.
This has meant more to me than you know.
Well, good.
I can't imagine how much your prayers
and your passion for God
must have meant to your husband.
Gosh, I wish I could've met him.
No.
No, you don't.
See, I wasn't the same woman back then.
When Leo died, we were not on good terms.
I always felt pushed to the back burner while
the military took first place in his life.
And I was... I was bitter, Elizabeth.
I was so bitter.
But even then,
God was showing me what to do.
He was prompting me to fight for Leo,
to pray for Leo, and I refused.
And I kept pushing it back
and pushing it back until it was too late.
And there's no grief as great
as denying the truth until it's too late.
It was my selfish pride, Elizabeth.
Oh, my selfish pride!
And I confessed it.
And I repented,
and I begged God to forgive me.
But I still have a scar.
And then I started spending more time
with the Lord,
and in His word.
And I learned how to fight
in prayer first.
I'm an old woman now.
And I realized that I have not passed on
what I had learned.
And when I last visited Leo's grave,
I asked God to send me someone
that I could help.
Someone that I could teach to fight
the right way.
And He sent me Elizabeth Jordan.
So you see, you...
You were the answer to my prayer.
Well, now you've got to teach other people
to seek the Lord.
You've got to teach other young wives
how to fight.
Yeah. I will.
I will.
- Mom, did you bring my snack?
- Oh, yeah, baby, I got it right here.
- Hey, Danielle, are you nervous?
- Very.
- Are you nervous?
- Oh, yeah!
But I'll be fine just as long as
I don't fall on my face.
Are you still gonna do that flip?
Yeah, I'm gonna do the flip.
And that's not all.
Huh, Danielle?
You ain't seen nothing yet, Liz.
Now I'm nervous.
Tony, isn't that Tom?
Yeah, it is.
Looks like a flat.
No. No! No. No, I can't wait that long!
Why do you promote helping out
in 30 minutes when it takes 45 to get here?
Listen, you guys stay put.
You know, I don't care. Just send someone!
Why did you do that?
'Cause that's how
I wanna be treated, Danielle.
Wow!
I'm so proud of you
for everything that you've done.
And I just can't wait to see
what you guys do out there.
- You wanna say something to them?
- Yeah, yeah.
Okay, good.
Listen, I just spoke
with the judges. Okay?
They've agreed to let us go last.
All right?
Yes!
Remember what we talked about?
We'll be the last thing they see.
We'll be impressive. All right?
Listen, I know you guys are nervous.
Believe me, lam, too.
But we're gonna take that nervous energy
and we're gonna turn it into rocket fuel.
- All right? You guys are with me?
- Yeah.
All right, let's blow them away.
Here we go. Comets on three.
All right, one, two, three.
Comets!
Welcome to the
Double Dutch Citywide Championship.
Who's ready for an awesome day?
All right. We're getting started right now
with the speed round. Here we go!
Raindrops rollin' off my brim.
Streetlights got the pavement glistenin'.
Touchdown, I fall into Your arms
Right where I belong.
Your everlasting arms...
All right, so the speed scores
will be added to the freestyle scores.
So let's start the freestyle competition.
First up is the Moon Jumpers.
And where would I be without You.
I'd be packin' my bags...
Next up is the Mustangs!
Chasin' every breeze that blows my way.
I'd be building my kingdom
just to watch it fade away.
I'd be packin' my bags
when I need to stay...
Now let's give it up
for the Tigers!
I'd be building my kingdom
just to watch it fade away.
It's true
That's me without You...
Here come the SkipSations!
That's me without You.
That's me.
That's me without You...
Now for the Speed Angels!
Flashback, step into the scene.
There's You and there's
a very different me.
Touchdown, You had me at believe.
You had me at believe, You did...
And where would I be.
Let's hear it
for the Super Skippers!
Without You.
I'd be packin' my
bags when I need to stay.
I'd be chasin' every
breeze that blows my way.
I'd be building my kingdom
just to watch it fade away.
It's true.
That's me without You.
And now for the final team
in our freestyle competition.
Let's hear it for the Comets!
There is no such, no such thing.
There is no such, no such thing
as impossible.
We can rise above the typical.
And be anything but usual.
We know, we know, we know.
That there's no such thing as impossible.
And nothing is unreachable.
When we trust the God of miracles.
We know, we know, we know.
That there's no such thing as impossible.
That's my dad! That's my dad!
The judges' scores are in.
In third place this year,
let's hear it for the Super Skippers!
And in second place, it was so close!
Let's hear it for the Comets!
And now our Double Dutch
Citywide Champions for this year,
let's hear it for the Speed Angels!
Hey, what are you doing?
- Hey, hey.
- What's going on?
I'll tell you in a minute, okay?
How was dinner?
Oh, it was good.
Cynthia actually agreed to meet with me
on a regular basis.
Good. Good.
- We'll try Tuesday afternoons to start.
- Okay.
Now listen, did they, uh, forgive me
for not helping them out?
Oh, yeah. I think so.
You know, they really appreciated
the $500 we gave them though.
I told her we really wanted to do more
but we just couldn't right now
- the way things are tight with money.
- Hmm.
She understood. But we did skip dessert.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, listen, I got something
I need to tell you. Okay?
Now I want you to think about it
before you respond, okay?
What is it?
I had an interview today.
And I got offered the job on the spot.
To do what?
To be the new director
at the community center.
Liz, we know this place so well. You know?
I'm telling you, I can do this job.
Gosh. You would be closer to home.
It's only half the pay,
but if we're wise, I know we can make it.
Listen to me.
I would rather have a man chasing Jesus
than a house full of stuff.
Okay.
All right, then I'll accept it.
You know what, I'm kind of glad
you didn't have that dessert tonight.
Why?
I got something for you.
Why don't you have a seat on the couch?
- What?
- Just head to the couch.
I got this, don't worry about it.
Where's Danielle?
She's fine. She's over at Jennifer's house.
They're having a sleepover. Yeah.
What is this?
You'll see.
No, no, no. Tony, don't touch my feet.
Hey. Just roll with it. Okay?
All right, come on now.
Oh, my goodness, it feels so good.
Now it's time I give you what you deserve.
This is for the woman I don't deserve.
You go ahead and work on that,
and I am gonna get started on that
foot massage you've been asking for.
Really?
- Are you really doing this for me?
- Yeah, come on now.
No, no, no, Tony!
I don't want you to smell my feet.
Babe, look. I told you, I got this.
You... Look.
You need to trust me, okay? So, like that.
I'm ready to go. You hear me?
- You're terrible.
- Yeah.
What's wrong?
I'm eating my favorite dessert
while my husband is rubbing my feet.
There has got to be a God in Heaven!
You've done it again, Lord.
You've done it again.
You are good and You are mighty
and You are merciful!
And You keep taking care of me
when I don't deserve it.
Praise You, Jesus!
You are Lord.
Give me another one, Lord.
Guide me to who You want me to help.
Raise up more that will
call upon Your name!
Raise up those that love You
and seek You and trust You!
Raise them up, Lord! Raise them up!
Lord, we need a generation of believers
who are not ashamed of the gospel.
We need an army of believers, Lord,
that hate to be lukewarm
and will stand on
Your word above all else.
Raise them up, Lord. Raise them up.
I pray for unity among
those that love You.
I pray that You open their eyes
so that they can see Your truth, Lord.
I pray for Your hand
of protection and guidance!
Raise up a generation, Lord,
that will take light into this world.
That will not compromise
when under pressure!
That will not cower, Lord,
when others fall away!
Raise them up, Lord,
that they will proclaim
that there is salvation
in the name of Jesus Christ!
Raise up warriors, Lord,
who will fight on their knees,
who will worship You
with their whole hearts, Lord.
Lord, call us to battle,
that we may proclaim You
King of Kings and Lord of Lords!
I pray these things with all my heart!
Raise them up, Lord! Raise them up!
I see the smoke on the horizon.
I feel my heart pounding in my chest.
I hear the war raging all around me.
But somehow I feel like
I was born for this.
I can taste or fee! The ageless courage.
As I raise my shield and lift my sword.
And I fall on my knees
and I fight like a warrior.
I am a warrior on my knees.
I call on the Name of the One
Who is Conqueror.
I'm only a conqueror when I believe.
The enemy trembles every time.
Because he knows the battle
is no longer mine.
When I fall on my knees
and I fight like a warrior.
Like a warrior, oh.
Daughters and sons
we can hear your calling.
Broken and weak, we can hear your cry.
And even though our enemy
roars like a lion.
The Lion of Judah is on our side.
And He will go before us and behind us.
Fighting on the left and on the right.
So I fall on my knees and
I fight like a warrior.
I am a warrior on my knees.
When I call on the Name of the One
Who is Conqueror.
I'm more than a conqueror when I believe.
The enemy trembles every time.
Because he knows the battle
is no longer mine.
But I fall on my knees
and I fight like a warrior.
Like a warrior.
Our weapons are trust
Our weapons are hope.
In the King of Kings
and the Lord of Lords.
"He says," I am with
you so don't be afraid.
"Because I have already won this war."
"So fall on your knees and fight with Me."
We are the warriors
when we are on our knees.
The enemy trembles.
We will fall on our knees
and fight like a warrior.
We are the warriors on our knees.
We call on the Name of the One
Who is Conqueror.
We're more than conquerors
when we believe.
The enemy trembles every time.
Because he knows
the battle isn't yours or mine.
When we fall on our knees
and fight like a warrior.
Like a warrior.
We are warriors on our knees.
We are the warriors.
We are warriors.
We are warriors on our knees.
Calling on the Name of Jesus.
Power in the Name of Jesus.
Power in the...
We will fall on our knees
and fight like a warrior.
We are the warriors on our knees.
We call on the Name of the One
Who is Conqueror.
We're more than conquerors
when we believe.
The enemy trembles every time.
Because he knows
the battle isn't yours or mine.
When we fall on our knees
and fight like a warrior.
Like a warrior.
We are warriors on our knees.
We are the warriors.
We are warriors.
We are warriors on our knees.
Calling on the Name of Jesus.
Power in the Name of Jesus.
Hope it helped -> bozxphd